//This function PUT to the API new data async function saveProductAPI(title, price, description, image, featured, form, formTitle) { const url = baseUrl + "/products/" + id;



- pkderlam.one/portfolio
- +47 93859246
- pkderlam@hotmail.com
- 💟 Trondheim Norway

Profile

I am punctual and tidy. I am honest,

responsible, efficient, reliable and trustworthy.

I have a good mood and a positive service attitude. I want to learn new skills and acquire work experience.

Skills

Ps Photoshop **፱** HTML React

■ CSS Wordpress Ai Illustrator

Strapi **B** Bootstrap Hotjar

JavaScript 🕅 Adobe GitHub

Sass mg npm Responsive Design

Languages

Portuguese - Native

English - B1

Norwegian - A2

Spanish - A1

Volunteer Work

Volunteer in COVID-19 vaccination in Trondheim - Jun, 2021 - Aug, 2021 / Dec, 2021 - Feb, 2022

Academic Background

Vocational Degree - Front-end Developer Noroff - Norway - (2020 - 2022)

Bachelor Degree - Law <u>UCS</u> - Brazil - (2013 - 2018)

Licentiate Degree - Portuguese and Brazilian Literature UFRGS - Brazil - (2008 - 2012)

Vocational Degree - Software System Development CETEC UCS - Brazil - (2002 - 2006)

Professional Experience

Police Officer (Dec 2014 - Aug 2020) at Polícia Civil do Rio Grande do Sul/Brazil

Portuguese Teacher (Feb 2014 - Jun 2014) at EMEF João de Zorzi at Caxias do Sul/Brazil

Portuguese Teacher (2012-2013) at EMEF Aracy Gomes Valim at Arroio do Sal/Brazil

Technical Assistant (Jun 2007 - Feb 2008) at MI Comércio e Servicos de Informática at Caxias do Sul/Brazil.

Projects



